Daryl Jason Lazaro

705 Canonbury Way Apt 383 Hayward, CA 94544 510-274-0769 daryl.lazaro@gmail.com

PROFILE

A driven self-starter with experience in teaching, customer service, and order fulfillment. Courteous and personable. Capable of transitioning back and forth between working independently, as a leader, and as a teammate. Requires minimal supervision and guidance to complete tasks according to protocol, or when troubleshooting as problems arise.

EXPERIENCE

Math Instructor, Grade 7-8 - 08/2015 - 06/2017

Our Lady of Guadalupe School (Fremont, CA)

Instructed 7th and 8th Grade normal-paced mathematics classes. Oversaw student learning and reinforcement of math concepts via student/teacher instruction and group activities. Created and implemented lesson plans according to 7th and 8th Grade *Go Math* textbook curriculum (Common Core Standards). Administered module quizzes and unit tests based on textbook material. Graded homework and classwork.

Integrated Khan Academy online math curriculum in both grades during the 2015-16 school year, and implemented *Go Math* online interactive learning resources in both grades during the 2016-17 school year.

Band & Orchestra Director — 02/2014 - 06/2017

Our Lady of Guadalupe School (Fremont, CA)

Managed the band and orchestra program with students ranging from 3rd to 8th grade. Provided instruction on violin, cello, flute, clarinet, oboe, alto saxophone, trumpet, baritone horn, and percussion. Conducted performances. Kept track of instrument inventory and rentals.

Starting with the 2014-15 school year, restructured the program into four sections (beginning and advanced for each group) to better meet the needs of each student's skill level. Raised the overall technicality of music performed in the Advanced groups to better prepare junior high musicians for high school performing arts programs.

Brass Clinician & Music Transcription Services - 07/2013 - 06/2017 Moreau Catholic High School (Hayward, CA)

Led weekly sectional classes for brass students ranging from 9th to 12th grade, for instruments including trombone, euphonium, tuba, trumpet, and French horn. Transcribed sheet music for the band program via Sibelius notation software.

Order Fulfillment: Packer/Shipper -08/2013 - 12/2015

Menus & Music (Emeryville, CA)

Picked stock from shelves to safely pack, protect, and ship orders in proper-sized shipping boxes. Lifted and moved heavy items (packages, stock) weighing up to 50 lbs. Printed and scanned shipping labels to be picked up by FedEx and USPS. Inspected products for defects. Received incoming shipments. Maintained shelf stock and clean work area.

VOLUNTEER

Faith Formation Catechist (Confirmation) = 09/2014 - 06/2017

Our Lady of Guadalupe Parish (Fremont, CA)

Instructed bi-monthly Confirmation classes for first-year and second-year Confirmation candidates. Created and implemented lesson plans according to *Decision Point* and *Called to be Christ* faith formation curricula. Supervised candidate attendance of church liturgies and mass services.

Helped start an English-speaking youth group for the parish in 2014, and a youth choir in 2017 for Sunday 6:00 PM mass services.

EDUCATION

University of California, Davis (Davis, CA) — BA English (Music minor), 09/2006 - 03/2011

SKILLS

Experience with Windows and Mac OS, Microsoft Office, Google Docs, multiple-subject education, customer service, tracking inventory, and fulfilling incoming/outgoing shipments.

REFERENCES

References are available upon request.